Guide to the Rice University's University Relations Audio-Video records, 1962-2005 UA 126
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University's University Relations Audio-Video records
1962-2005
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 126
9.5 Linear Feet (13 boxes)
Audio and video related to the daily work of the Rice University Office of University Relations.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of University Relations at Rice University, also known as Public Affairs, is charged with collaborating closely with local organizations and individuals to communicate Rice's plans and priorities to our Houston neighbors while also striving to understand what's most important to them and share that perspective with university leaders.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes audio and video related to the daily work of the Office of University Relations. Much of the material was created by Rice University, and in some cases by other Houston entities.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges
Document Types
videotapes; audiotapes
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University -- History
- Series I: University Promotional Videos, 1990-2005, 149192
  - Rice Video Profiles TRT: 30 min, 24 Oct 1990 (2 Copies), 149200 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Rice Video Profiles (1st Copy) TRT: 30 min, 24 Oct 1990, 149201 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Rice Video Profiles (2nd Copy) TRT: 30 min, 24 Oct 1990, 149202 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Rice Video Profiles (3rd Copy) TRT: 30 min, 24 Oct 1990, 149203 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Campus Shots and Aerials- Rice University (Video 3 of 4), 1990, 149204 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Rice University: Letters, Science, and Art, Fall 1991, 149205 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Rice University: Letters, Science, and Art (Centennial Slide Presentation), Fall 1991, 149206 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Rice University: Letters, Science, and Art (Video 1 of 2), Fall 1991, 149207 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Rice University: Letters, Science, and Art (Video 3 of 5), Fall 1991, 149208 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Rice University: Letters, Science, and Art (Video 4 of 5), Fall 1991, 149209 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Rice's 'Best Buy' Ranking (Video 1 of 1), 17 Apr 1992, 149210 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Rice's 'Best Buy' Ranking (Video 2 of 2), 17 Apr 1992, 149211 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Rice's 'Best Buy' Ranking (Video 1 of 1), KCS-20BRS, 17 Apr 1992, 149212 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Rice University Campus Shots and Aerials " Rice Univ. Demo"; Produced for press in prep for German president's visit at commencement, 1992, 149213 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - S. Malcolm Gillis Presidential Announcement Press Conference, 2 June 1993, 149214 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Fox News- Jobless Grads (For Rice Self Promo Use - Not For Broadcast Use), 18 June 1993, 149215 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Fiske Interactive Guide: Rice University (Video 2 of 2), 24 Feb 1994, 149216 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Fiske Interactive Guide Audio Track for Video (7 Takes), 24 Feb 1994, 149217 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - The Architecture of Rice (Old Version), c. 1994, 149218 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - The Architecture of Rice (Video 1 of 2), 24 Apr 1994, 149219 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - The Architecture of Rice (Video 2 of 2), 24 Apr 1994, 149220 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - The Architecture of Rice DUB Master, TRT: 16 min 50 sec, Beta T-30, 24 Apr 1994, 149221 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Rice University: "Faces of Rice" TRT: 30 sec, 15 Aug 1995 (2 Copies), 149228 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Rice University: "Faces of Rice" (Video 1 of 5), 9 Feb 1996, 149229 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Rice University: "Faces of Rice" (Video 2 of 5), 9 Feb 1996, 149230 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Rice University: "Faces of Rice" (Video 3 of 5), 9 Feb 1996, 149231 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Rice University: "Faces of Rice" (Video 5 of 5), 9 Feb 1996, 149232 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Rice Institutional - Film Transfer (Matching Time-Code Window Burn) TRT: 39 min, 17 Sept 1996, 149233 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Rice University- Michol, Marcela, Jermaine, Roland, Larry in Baker Study, 24 June 1997, 149234 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Rice University Admissions Video TRT: 14 min 30 sec, 15 Sept 1997 (5 Copies), 149235 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Rice University Admissions Video TRT: 14 min, 1997 (3 Copies), 149236 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Frame by Frame: Rice University, Produced for the Office of Admissions, 1997, 149237 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Granite House Rice University Promotion TRT: 15 sec, 10 Sept 1998 (Beta T-5 & Beta T-D32), 149238 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Texas State Fair Promo, Rice University, Beta T-30, 1998, 149239 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Rice University TRT: 2 min, 47 sec, Beta T-5, 2 Dec 1999, 149240 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Rice University "Through the Sallyport", Tape #1, TRT: 1 min, Beta SP, 8 Apr 2000, 149241 (Box 2, Folder -)
  - Continental Airlines Rice University Edit Piece, 14 Sept 2001, 149245 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Continental Airlines Rice University Edit Piece + B-Roll from Shoot, Betacam SP-90, 14 Sept 2001, 149246 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Marshall Rice Tour, 2002, 149247 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Bond Campaign, 149248 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Dr. Malcolm Gillis Revised PSAs TRT: 30 sec, 149249 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions: Smalley, Tape 1, 149250 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions Video: Edit Master, 149251 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Campaign: The Next Century (2 Copies), 149252 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice University Baker Institute Helicopter Footage, 149253 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice University Demo, B-Roll, 149254 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice University Generic Intro, U-Matic, 149255 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Stude Concert Hall Video Tour: Shepherd School of Music, 149256 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - A Tribute to H. Malcolm Lovett, 149257 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 1 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 19 Feb 2005, 149260 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 2 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 19 Feb 2005, 149261 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 3 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 19 Feb 2005, 149262 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 4 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 19 Feb 2005, 149263 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 5 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 19 Feb 2005, 149264 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 6 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 19 Feb 2005, 149265 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 7 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 19 Feb 2005, 149266 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 8 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 19 Feb 2005, 149267 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 9 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 20 Feb 2005, 149268 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 10 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 20 Feb 2005, 149269 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 11 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 22 Feb 2005, 149270 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 12 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 20 Feb 2005, 149271 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 13 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 22Feb 2005, 149272 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 14 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, Feb 2005, 149273 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 15 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, Feb 2005, 149274 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 16 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 20 Feb 2005, 149275 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 17 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 20 Feb 2005, 149276 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 18 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, 20 Feb 2005, 149277 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions B-Roll (Tape 19 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, Feb 2005, 149278 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice Admissions (Tape 20 of 20) Ttweak, DVCAM 40, Feb 2005, 149279 (Box 3, Folder -)
  - Rice History—5 Photo Negatives, 149280 (Box 3, Folder -)
- Series II: News Segments, 1988-2001, 149193
  - Newsweek on Air: Stalking Alumni (Audio Cassette 1 of 8), 28 Aug 1988, 149281 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Newsweek on Air: Stalking Alumni (Audio Cassette 2 of 8), 28 Aug 1988, 149282 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Newsweek on Air: Stalking Alumni (Audio Cassette 3 of 8), 28 Aug 1988, 149283 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Newsweek on Air: Stalking Alumni (Audio Cassette 4 of 8), 28 Aug 1988, 149284 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Newsweek on Air: Stalking Alumni (Audio Cassette 5 of 8), 28 Aug 1988, 149285 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Newsweek on Air: Stalking Alumni (Audio Cassette 6 of 8), 28 Aug 1988, 149286 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Newsweek on Air: Stalking Alumni (Audio Cassette 7of 8), 28 Aug 1988, 149287 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Newsweek on Air: Stalking Alumni (Audio Cassette 8 of 8), 28 Aug 1988, 149288 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Broadcast News Reports: "RE: Date Rape"; Rice Play "Mixed Signals", KRC-TV (CH. 2) 5 PM News with Bill Balleza and Dr. Dixie Swanson, Beta, 23 Aug 1990, 149289 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Broadcast News Reports: "RE: Date Rape"; Rice Play "Mixed Signals", KTRK-TV (CH. 13) 11 AM "Home Show" with Gary Collins TRT: 14 min, 10 Sept 1990, 149290 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Broadcast News Reports: "RE: Pollution Poll" KPRC-TV (CH. 2) 5 PM News, KTRK-TV (CH. 13) 6 PM News, KHOU-TV (CH. 11) 6 PM News, KHTV-TV (CH. 39) 7 PM News, 1 Oct 1990, 149291 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Broadcast News Reports: "RE: Texas Environmental Survey" KXAN-TV (CH. 36) 6PM (Austin), 1 Oct 1990, 149292 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Broadcast News Reports: "RE: Date Rape"; Rice Play "Mixed Signals", KHOU-TV (CH. 11) 5 PM News with Marlene McClinton and Philip Bruce, 11 Oct 1990, 149293 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Broadcast News Reports: "RE: Royal Visit" KTRK-TV (CH. 13) 6 PM News with Shara Fryer and KHOU-TV (CH. 11) 6 PM News with Clare Casademont concerning Prince Akishino of Japan, 26 Apr 1991, 149294 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Broadcast News Reports: "RE: America 2000" KTRK-TV (CH. 13) 5 PM News with Melanie Lawson and Alan Hemberger and KHOU-TV (CH. 11) 5 PM News with Steve Smith and Nancy Holland, 2 Mar 1992, 149295 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Broadcast News Reports: "RE: Billy Graham" KUHT-TV (CH.8) 6PM "MacNeil/ Lehrer Report" with Richard Ostling TRT: 16 min, 17 Apr 1992, 149296 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - ABC Special Viewpoint with Ted Koppel - Politics & Media: Reporting or Distorting, 16 Sept 1992, 149297 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - ABC Special Viewpoint with Ted Koppel - Politics & Media: Reporting or Distorting, Beta T-90GL, 16 Sept 1992, 149298 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Eyewitness News KTRK Houston "City Building Department Controversy" TRT 4:52, 2 Feb 1994, 149299 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - "Dr. Ruth South Lowry" Eleven News at Noon KHOU-TV (CBS) Houston, 12:00-12:30pm TRT: 2 min 49 sec, 12 May 1995 and "Esther Julicher" Steve Smith's Sunday KHOU-TV (CBS) Houston, 9:30-10:30am TRT: 3 min 22 sec, 14 May 1995, 149300 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - Broadcast News Reports: James Baker Dedication, CH. 26, 2, 13, and 11, 15 Oct 1997, 149301 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - "Marching Band" Wheel of Fortune (Syndicated) TRT: 30 min, 11 May 1998, 149302 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - "Rice Student" Wheel of Fortune (Syndicated) TRT: 30 min, 12 May 1998, 149303 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - "Baker Institute" Weeknight Edition, KUHT-TV (PBS) Houston 5:30-6:30pm TRT: 15 min 56 sec, 12 June 1998, 149304 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - ABC-13 "1998 Best of the Class" (2 Copies), 149305 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - "Top Colleges" World News Tonight, ABC-TV Network TRT: 4 min 59 sec, 25 Sept 1999, 149306 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - Channel 11 5PM News: Rice's Student Run EMS, 18 Aug 2000, 149307 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - News Hour with Jim Lehrer (McNeil); CNN (Djerjian); BBC's Tomorrow's World (Braam); Channel 11 (EMS Students), c. 2000, 149308 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - MBN Channel 20 TV (Korean), 26 Jan 2001, 149309 (Box 5, Folder -)
- Series III: University Events, 1962; 1991-2004, 149310
  - President John F. Kennedy Speech at Rice Stadium Launching Space Program, 12 Sept 1962 (2 Copies), 149311 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - Rice Homecoming (Video 1 of 5), 1991, 149312 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - Rice Homecoming (Video 2 of 5), 1991, 149313 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - Rice Homecoming (Video 3 of 5), 1991, 149314 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - Rice Homecoming (Video 4 of 5), 1991, 149315 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - Rice Homecoming (Video 5 of 5), 1991, 149316 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - Visit of President Dudaev, Republic of Chechen, 19 Oct 1992, 149317 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - First Annual Senior Picnic, 29 Apr 1993, 149318 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - Baker College Graduation, 1993, 149319 (Box 5, Folder -)
  - Jimmy Carter Commencement Speech, 8 May 1993, 149320 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Jimmy Carter Commencement Speech (Video 2 of 4), 8 May 1993, 149321 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Jimmy Carter Commencement Speech (Video 3 of 4), 8 May 1993, 149322 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Jimmy Carter Commencement Speech (Video 4 of 4), 8 May 1993, 149323 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Jimmy Carter Commencement Speech (Video 5 of 5), 8 May 1993, 149324 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Jimmy Carter Commencement Speech, T-30 Beta, 8 May 1993, 149325 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Will Rice College Advisor's Meeting, 15 Sept 1993, 149326 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Freshman Matriculation (Video 1 of 2), 17 Aug 1993, 149327 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Freshman Matriculation (Video 2 of 2), 17 Aug 1993, 149328 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Freshman Matriculation II, 17 Aug 1993, 149329 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Freshman Matriculation III (Audio Cassette), 17 Aug 1993, 149330 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Pres. Gillis: Speech to Friends of Fondren, 24 May 1994, 149331 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Stephen Klineberg: Faculty Address, 22 Aug 1994, 149332 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Freshman Matriculation, 26 Aug 1994, 149333 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Freshman Matriculation (Audio Cassette), 26 Aug 1994, 149334 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Willy's Birthday, 1995, 149335 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Rice University Commencement TRT: 2 hrs. 30 min, 13 May 1995 (2 Copies), 149336 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Rice University Commencement Exercises including Senator Bill Bradley, Marshall Gramm & Senator Phil Gramm, Esther Julicher, and B-Roll, Beta T-30, 13 May 1995, 149337 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Rice University Commencement: Procession and Recession, 13 May 1995, 149338 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Rice University Graduation and Commencement, Access Houston Footage (Tape 1 of 3), 13 May 1995, 149339 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Rice University Graduation and Commencement, Access Houston Footage (Tape 2 of 3), 13 May 1995, 149340 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Rice University Graduation and Commencement, Access Houston Footage (Tape 3 of 3), 13 May 1995, 149341 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Rice University Commencement (Part 1 of 2) TRT: 90 min, T-90 Beta, 13 May 1995, 149342 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Rice University Commencement (Part 2 of 2), TRT: 60 min, T-90 Beta, 13 May 1995, 149343 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - HENNAC Award—"Hispanic Engineer of the Year", Richard Tapia, 12 October 1996, 149344 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - A Tribute to Charles and Anne Duncan, 12 December 1996, 149345 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Anne and Charles Duncan Hall Dedication, c. 1996, 149346 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Knight Line Productions: Rice Rodeo, 1996, 149347 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - CNT Laboratory Opening (Audio Cassette), 17 Aug 1999, 149348 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Rice Matriculation Ceremony, 22 Aug 1999, 149349 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Faculty Address TRT: 21 min, 23 Aug 1999, 149350 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Martel Groundbreaking, T-30 Beta, 10 Apr 2000, 149351 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Commemoration of the 40th Anniversary of President John F. Kennedy's Address at Rice University TRT: 1 hr. 37 min, 23 Sept 2001, 149352 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Congressman Culberson Visit- CS Camp, 28 June 2004, 149353 (Box 7, Folder -)
- Series IV: Baker Institute Events, 1993-2003, 149545
  - Baker Institute News Conference, 22 Jan 1993, 149546 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Baker Institute Lecture: James A. Baker III – I Beta T-30 (Tape 1 of 2), 30 Sept 1993, 149547 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Baker Institute Lecture: James A. Baker III – I Beta T-30 (Tape 2 of 2), 30 Sept 1993, 149548 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Baker Institute Lecture: James A. Baker III – I, (Tape 1 of 3), KCS-20BRS, 30 Sept 1993, 149549 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Baker Institute Lecture: James A. Baker III – I, (Tape 2 of 3), KCS-20BRS, 30 Sept 1993, 149550 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Baker Institute Lecture: James A. Baker III – I, (Tape 3 of 3), KCS-20BRS, 30 Sept 199, 149551 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Baker Institute Lecture: James A. Baker, III – II, 30 Sept 1993, 149552 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Baker Institute Lecture: James A. Baker, III – III, 30 Sept 1993, 149553 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Baker Institute Lecture: James A. Baker III—Cohen House Reception Line, B-Roll, Beta T-30, 30 Sept 1993, 149554 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Baker Institute Lecture: James A. Baker III (Audio Cassette), 30 Sept 1993, 149555 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - HUGO Genome International Summit (Video 1 of 1), 22 Jan 1994, 149556 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - HUGO Genome International Summit (Video 1 of 2), 22 Jan 1994, 149557 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - HUGO Genome International Summit (Video 2 of 2), 22 Jan 1994, 149558 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Baker Institute Lecture: HUGO Summit (Audio Cassette), 22 Jan 1994, 149559 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - James A. Baker III Institute For Public Policy "Baker Inst. Inaugural Conference: Enron Prize Presentation" (Panel #2 Tape 1), 13 Oct 1995, 149561 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy Third Annual Conference "United States Foreign Policy Priorities on the Eve of the 21st Century" (Tape 1) TRT: 3 hours and 3 min, 16 Oct 1997, 149562 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy Third Annual Conference " United States Foreign Policy Priorities on the Eve of the 21st Century" (Tape 2) TRT: 29 minutes 32 sec, 16 Oct 1997, 149563 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy Third Annual Conference "U.S. Foreign Policy Priorities Eve of 21st Century" (Various), 16 Oct 1997, 149564 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - James A. Baker III Institute For Public Policy " Presentation of Enron Prize to Nelson Mandela & Prince Bandar Bin Sultan", 26 Oct 1999, 149565 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - James A. Baker III Institute For Public Policy "Review of Non oil Gas Research in the Houston- Galveston-Gulf Coast Area" Mitchell, Smalley, Holtzapple, Hennekes, Chang-Diaz (Video 1 of 2), 4 Dec 2003, 149568 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - James A. Baker III Institute For Public Policy "Review of Non oil Gas Research in the Houston- Galveston-Gulf Coast Area" Mitchell, Smalley, Holtzapple, Hennekes, Chang-Diaz (Video 2 of 2), 149569 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Rice Ambassador TRN, #1, James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy, 149570 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Rice Ambassador TRN #2, James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy, 149571 (Box 9, Folder -)
- Series V: Educational/Academic Videos, 1987-2002, 149573
  - The Research Challenge: Joyce Gar Report. 5 Nov 1987, 149580 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - EPA: "What it Means to You" A Videotape on the Emergency Planning and Community Right to Know Act TRT: 15 min, 1990, 149581 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - "Take Care" Women's Health, 22 Sept 1992, 149582 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Gale Stokes on Bosnia, 6 Oct 1992, 149583 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - UR. EVE: Klineberg/SW Bell FOCUS 93 News Conference, 29 Mar 1993, 149584 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Dr. Alexander J. Dessler: "Dynamics of Jupiter's Plasma Nebula", 29 Apr 1993, 149585 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - The Final Forum: TX US Sen. Race Debate, 29 Apr 1993, 149586 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Gillis Inauguration Symposium, 30 Oct 1993, 149587 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Understanding NAFTA…Part I (Video 1 of 2), 22 Mar 1994, 149588 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Understanding NAFTA…Part II (Video 2 of 2), 22 Mar 1994, 149589 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Lecture: The Hon. P.V. Narasimha Rao, 16 May 199, 149590 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - President's Lecture Series: Richard Staar (Audio Cassette), 2 Nov 1994, 149591 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Parallel Computing at Work: CRPC Activities in Collaboration, Knowledge Transfer, and Education TRT: 19 min., 9 Nov 1994 (2 Copies), 149592 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Groundbreaking Ceremonies: George Bush Presidential Library Center TRT: 18 min, 30 Nov 1994, 149593 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - George Bush Talks about His Presidential Library (Video 1 of 2), c. 1994, 149594 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - George Bush Talks about His Presidential Library (Video 2 of 2), c. 1994, 149595 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - CRPC "Parallel Computation Makes for Good Vibrations" TRT: 11 min 20 sec, 20 Sept 1995, 149603 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Hoby Story "Short Version", 1995, 149604 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Firing Line Debate "The Environmentalists Have Gone Too Far Too Fast" at Rice University TRT: 117 min (2 Copies), 14 Mar 1997, 149605 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Unedited footage IUB Press Conference Provided by Radio Bremen TV, 12 Feb 1999, 149606 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Bremen International University Footage, T-30 Beta (Video 1 of 2), 2 Sept 1999, 149607 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Bremen International University Footage, T-30 Beta (Video 2 of 2), 2 Dec 1999, 149608 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Rice University/Grundung aus "Buten un Binnen", Radio Bremen, 2 Dec 1999, 149609 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - "Invest in the Future", The Science Coalition, TRT: 6 min 35 sec., 11 July 200, 149610 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Savings Bonds TRT: 3 min. 56 sec., 2002, 149611 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Bill Martin in Sewell Office, Part 1 of Criminology Class, Large Lecture, T-30 Beta, 4 Apr, 149612 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - "ERC" Electronic Brochure Al Kahn Group, Inc., 149613 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - The Great American West TRT: 41 min, 149614 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Teachers' Workshop: Bridging Cultures Part 1, 149615 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Teachers' Workshop: Bridging Cultures Part 2, 149616 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Texas A&M: Sterling C. Evans Library, 149617 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - The U.S. Congress & You, U.S. Congressman Glenn English, 149618 (Box 10, Folder -)
- Series VI: Athletics, 1991-1997, 149622
  - Southwest Conference: Rice Halftime Spots (Video 1 of 2), 12 Sept 1991, 149623 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Southwest Conference: Rice Halftime Spots, Beta T-30 (Video 2 of 2), c. 1991, 149624 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Southwest Conference Promos, Texas A&M University (Audio Cassette 1 of 2), 1992, 149625 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Southwest Conference Promos, Texas A&M University (Audio Cassette 2 of 2), 1992, 149626 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Mayor Lanier's Comments on UH-Rice/SWC Issue, 23 Feb 1994, 149627 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Rice Homecoming Football Game, 2 Nov 1996, 149628 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Rice University TV WAC Video Rough Edits TRT: 3 X 30 sec, 16 July 1996, 149629 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Rice University WAC Promo Spot TRT: 30 sec, c. 1996, 149630 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Rice University WAC Promo Master, c. 1996, 149631 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Rice vs. Air Force Aerials of Campus and Stadium, 6 Sept 1997, 149632 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - 80 Years of Excellence in Rice Athletics, 149633 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - ESPN College Game Day Rice Segment, 149634 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Men's and Women's Swimming; Men's Track; Women's and Men's Tennis; Men's and Women's B-Ball; Football; Women's Track, 149635 (Box 11, Folder -)
- Series VII: Interviews, 1997-2000, 149636
  - "Becky Lee's Diary" Richard Tapia Guest, June 1997, 149637 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Bob McNair Interview, Rice University (Tape 1 of 8) Beta T-30, 1 June 2000, 149638 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Bucky Allshouse Interview, Rice University (Tape 2 of 8) Beta T-30, 1 June 2000, 149639 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Kent Anderson Interview, Rice University (Tape 3 of 8) T-30 Beta, 1 June 2000, 149640 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Dr. Bowles Interview, Rice University (Tape 4 of 8) Beta T-30, 1 June 2000, 149641 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Malcolm Gillis Interview, Rice University (Tape 5 of 8) Beta T-30, 1 June 2000, 149642 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Carol Quillen Interview, Rice University (Tape 6 of 8) Beta T-30, 2 June 2000, 149643 (Box 11, Folder -)